nigeriagoldexchange.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy - NigeriaGoldExchange.ng | Instant Payment | Fund, Buy, Sell, Exchange and Bid | Perfect Money, Egopay, Webmoney, Skrill, PayPal, SolidTrustPay, Payza, Ukash, CashU, Bitcoin, HotForex, Exness and PexPay | Virtual Credit Cards

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy explains the data processing practices of Demo. By using service of Demo or registering, you expressly consent to us collecting, using and disclosing of your personal information in the order described in present Privacy Policy. If you have any queries concerning your personal data or any requests in respect of these practices, please feel free to contact us via email at sales@Demo any time. 

#### Data Protection

* * *

This Privacy Policy applies to all countries we work with. Personal information is collected when you provide personal data to the website Demo, for example when you register, verify your Ultimate System (Process Pay) account, simply use Demo services or sending an e-mail to the site through the use of Contact Us forms. We do not keep copies of provided documents. To protect copies of your documents from using it with other purposes than identifying your personality at Demo, you can use watermark option http://www.watermark.ws/ or http://picmarkr.com/

#### We use this personal data to:

* * *

  * identify your personality for secure transaction
  * improve the content of our site
  * provide you with a more personalized service
  * perform market research
  * send you, via e-mail, telephone, SMS and post, special offers and promotions
  * share aggregated information with third parties (such as our merchant partners) for both advertising and promotional purposes. We will not pass on your individual contact details unless you have given us specific permission to do so
  * hold your data for security administration, legal and maintenance purposes.
